Karen Shearer Collection, 1935-1996, bulk 1974-1992
Indiana University Digital Library Program
- 2. Rock Chronicles (radio program), 1967-1996
  - 2.1. Rock Chronicles Interview and Program Transcripts, 1978-1994
    - Beck, Jeff, 1985 August, 22 typed leaves
      Interview with Jeff Beck.
    - Blue Öyster Cult (Musical group), 1981 July 27, 33 typed leaves
      Interview with [Eric Bloom?].
    - Blue Öyster Cult (Musical group), undated, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with [Donald "Buck Dharma" Roser?].
    - Brannen, John, 1988 February 17, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with John Brannen, summary notes.
    - BulletBoys (Musical group), 1988 November 21, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with Mick Sweda and Lonnie Vincent, summary notes.
    - Burtnick, Glen, 1987 September 14, 17 typed leaves
      Interview with Glen Burtnick.
    - Cafferty, John, 1980s, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with John Cafferty, summary notes.
    - Cafferty, John, 1980s, 2 typed leaves
    - Call (Musical group), 1989 June 6, 2 typed leaves
      Interview questions for The Call.
    - Cheap Trick (Musical group), 1982 May 10, 22 typed leaves
      Interview with Robin Zander.
    - Collins, Phil, 1981 February 18, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with Phil Collins, summary notes.
    - Collins, Phil, 1985 January 17, 2 typed leaves
    - Collins, Phil, 1983 March 24, 3 typed leaves
    - Collins, Phil, 1982 December 20, 35 typed leaves
      Interview with Phil Collins.
    - Costello, Elvis, 1982 July 26, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with Elvis Costello, summary notes.
    - Costello, Elvis, 1980s, 2 typed leaves
    - Costello, Elvis, 1986 February 17, 2 typed leaves
    - Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young, 1983 March 24, 39 typed leaves
      Interview with Graham Nash and Stephen Stills.
    - Culture Club (Musical group), 1983 September 6, 31 typed leaves
      Interview with Boy George.
    - Culture Club (Musical group), 1983 November 28, 33 typed leaves
    - Culture Club (Musical group), 1983 March 9, 29 typed leaves
      Interview with Boy George and John Suede.
    - Dokken, 1988 January 4, 6 typed leaves
      Interview with Don Dokken and Jeff Pilson.
    - Eurythmics (Musical group), 1988 August 10, 8 typed leaves
      Interview with Annie Lennox and Dave Stewart, summary notes.
    - Fleetwood Mac (Musical group), 1982 July, 32 typed leaves
      Interview with Mick Fleetwood and Christine McVie.
    - Flock of Seagulls (Musical group), 1982 June 12, 6 typed leaves
      Interview with Mike Score and Ali Score, summary notes.
    - Hagar, Sammy, 1982 April 1, 4 typed leaves
      Interview with Sammy Hagar, summary notes.
    - Hall and Oates (Musical group), 1983 December 6, 12 typed leaves
      Interview with Darryl Hall.
    - Hall and Oates (Musical group), 1984 March 8, 8 typed leaves
      Interview with Darryl Hall and John Oates.
    - Hall and Oates (Musical group), 1981 October 5, 21 typed leaves
    - Hall and Oates (Musical group), 1983 October 6, 16 typed leaves
    - Hall and Oates (Musical group), 1985 April 29, 33 typed leaves
    - Hall and Oates (Musical group), 1985 July 3, 19 typed leaves
    - Human League (Musical group), 1982 May 13, 8 typed leaves
      Interview with Adrian Wright and Jo Callis, summary notes.
    - Idol, Billy, 1980s, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with Billy Idol, summary notes.
    - Information Society (Musical group), 1988 July 28, 10 typed leaves
      Interview with Amanda Kramer and [James Cassidy?], summary notes.
    - J. Geils Band, 1980s, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with Peter Wolf, summary notes.
    - J. Geils Band, 1980s, 4 typed leaves
      Interview with Peter Wolf and Seth Justman, summary notes.
    - Jethro Tull (Musical group), 1987 October 9, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with Ian Anderson, summary notes.
    - John Cafferty and the Beaver Brown Band (Musical Group), 1980s, 3 typed leaves
    - Judas Priest (Musical group), 1982 November 22, 30 typed leaves
      Interview with Rob Halford.
    - Kasem, Casey, 1993 December 16, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with Casey Kasem, summary notes.
    - Kasem, Casey, circa 1993, 5 typed leaves
      Notes for interview with Casey Kasem.
    - Kinks (Musical group), 1981 May 18, 27 typed leaves
      Interview with Dave Davies.
    - Kiss (Musical group), 1994 January 20, 16 typed leaves
      Interview with Gene Simmons for History of Rock n' Roll; Andrew Solt Productions.
    - Martin, George interview notes, 1980s, 5 leaves
    - McCartney, Paul, 1982 May 4, 31 typed leaves
      Interview with Paul McCartney.
    - Missing Persons (Musical group), 1982 August 9, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with Terry Bozzio, Dale Bozzio and Warren Cuccurullo, summary notes.
    - Motels (Musical group), 1985 July, 33 leaves
      Interview with Martha Davis.
    - Mötley Crüe (Musical group), 1980s, 4 typed leaves (Box 45)
      "My Top Ten" with Nikki Sixx--Program transcript.
    - Mötley Crüe (Musical group), 1990 March, 3 typed leaves
      Interview notes with [Vince Neil?].
    - Nugent, Ted-, 1982 June 24, 29 typed leaves
      Interview with Ted Nugent.
    - Oingo Boingo (Musical group), 1980s, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with [Danny Elfman?], summary notes.
    - Oldfield, Mike, 1980s, 9 typed leaves
      Interview with Mike Oldfield.
    - Osbourne, Ozzy, 1981 November 14, 36 typed leaves
      Interview with Ozzy Osbourne.
    - Osbourne, Ozzy, 1983 January 6, 27 typed leaves
    - Osbourne, Ozzy, 1984 January 19, 6 typed leaves
      Interview with Ozzy Osbourne, summary notes.
    - Petty, Tom, 1982 November 9, 42 typed leaves
      Interview with Tom Petty.
    - Poison (Musical group), 1988 June 3, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with Brett Michaels, summary notes.
    - Poison (Musical group), 1980s, 4 typed pages
      Interview with C.C. Deville and Bobby Dall.
    - Power Station (Musical group), 1985 March 15, 24 typed leaves
      Interview with John Taylor and Robert Palmer.
    - Power Station (Musical group), 1985 December 3, 36 typed leaves
      Interview with Michael Des Barres.
    - Power Station (Musical group), 1985 July, 23 typed leaves
    - Pretenders (Musical group), 1983 February 1, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with Martin Chambers, summary notes.
    - Psychedelic Furs (Musical group), 1983 March 8, 1 typed leaf
      Interview with Tim Butler, summary notes.
    - Queen (Musical group), 1981 September 26, 31 typed leaves
      Interview with Freddie Mercury.
    - Rainbow (Musical group), 1981 April, 7 typed leaves
      Interview with Richie Blackmore, also summary notes.
    - Rainbow (Musical group), 1981 March 22, 15 typed leaves + notes (1 leaf)
      Interview with Roger Glover.
    - Ramones (Musical group), 1980s, 2 typed leaves
      Interview with Joey Ramone, summary notes.
    - REO Speedwagon (Musical group), 1982 May 18, 9 typed leaves
      Interview with Gary Richrath, summary notes.
    - REO Speedwagon (Musical group), 1982 May 18, 60 typed leaves
      Interview with Kevin Cronin and Gary Richrath.
    - Robertson, Robbie, 1982 June 14, 11 typed leaves
      Interview with Robbie Robertson.
    - Rolling Stones, 1980s, #? typed leaves
      Special of the Week program transcript.
    - Rolling Stones: Bill Wyman, 1983 February 11, 53 typed leaves + tape index summary
      Rolling Stones: Bill Wyman interview.
    - Rolling Stones: Bill Wyman, 1989 October, [EXTENT?]
      Rolling Stones: Bill Wyman interview and transcript summaries.
    - Rolling Stones: Bill Wyman, 1981, 12 typed leaves
      Rolling Stones: Bill Wyman interview with Terry Atkinson.
    - Rolling Stones: Keith Richards and Ron Woods, 1978 September 18, 43 typed leaves
      Rolling Stones: Keith Richards and Ron Woods interview with Alan Goldblatt.
    - Rolling Stones: Keith Richards, 1981 May, 56 typed leaves
      Rolling Stones: Keith Richards interview.
    - Rolling Stones: Mick Jagger and Keith Richards, 1989 October 8, 21 typed leaves
      Rolling Stones: Mick Jagger and Keith Richards interview.
    - Rolling Stones: Mick Jagger and Ron Woods, 1983 February 11, 28 typed leaves
      Rolling Stones: Mick Jagger and Ron Woods interview.
    - Rolling Stones: Mick Jagger, 1978 August 16, 34 typed leaves
      Rolling Stones: Mick Jagger interview with Alan Goldblatt.
    - Rolling Stones: Mick Jagger, 1982 April 22, 31 typed leaves
      Rolling Stones: Mick Jagger interview with David Pritchard and Alan Lysaght.
    - Roth, David Lee, 1955-, undated, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with David Lee Roth, summary notes.
    - Roth, David Lee, 1955-, 1994 January 26, 3 typed leaves
    - Rundgren, Todd, 1980s, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with Todd Rundgren, summary notes.
    - Scandal (Musical group), 1983 March 8, 4 typed leaves
      Interview with Patty Smyth and Zak Smith, summary notes.
    - Scorpions (Musical group), 1980s, 2 typed leaves
      Interview notes with Klaus Meine, summary notes.
    - Seger, Bob, 1980 April 30, 45 typed leaves
      Interview with Bob Seger.
    - Seger, Bob, 1983 April 22, 37 typed leaves
    - Shapiro, Bill, 1988 June 30, 5 typed leaves
      Interview with Bill Shapiro, summary notes.
    - Smith, Joe (former President of Capitol/EMI), 1993 December 15, 6 typed leaves
      Interview questions for Joe Smith, former President of Capitol/EMI, summary notes.
    - Split Enz (Musical group), 1980s, [EXTENT?]
      Interview with Tim Finn and Noel Crombie, summary notes.
    - Stewart, Rod, 1980s, 6 typed leaves (Box 46)
      Program transcript with Rod Stewart.
    - Stewart, Rod, 1988 December, 2 typed leaves
      Program transcript of The Source Radio Network presents the London Profile of Rod Stewart.
    - Stewart, Rod, 1981 October 6, 48 typed leaves
      Interview with Rod Stewart.
    - Stewart, Rod, 1983 April 13, 33 typed leaves
    - Sting (Musician), 1980s, 7 typed leaves
      Article from interview material with Sting.
    - Styx (Musical group), 1981 February 28, 6 typed leaves
      Interview with Tommy Shaw, summary notes.
    - Toto (Musical group), 1983 March 4, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with Jeff Porcaro, summary notes.
    - Toto (Musical group), 1981 August 31, 1 typed leaf
      Interview with Mike Porcaro, summary notes.
    - Triumph (Musical group), 1981 August 17, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with Mike Levine, summary notes.
    - Triumph (Musical group), 1983 February 28, 2 typed leaves
    - Tubes (Musical group), 1983 April 6, 4 typed leaves
      Interview with Fee Waybill, summary notes.
    - Van Halen (Musical group), 1982 May 27, 28 typed leaves
      Interview with David Lee Roth and Alex Van Halen.
    - Vanderberg (Musical group), 1980s, 5 typed leaves
      Interview with Adrian Vandenberg, summary notes.
    - Whitesnake (Musical group), 1980s, 24 typed leaves
      Interview with David Coverdale and Jon Lord.
    - Who (Musical group), 1982 October 2, 26 typed leaves
      Interview with John Entwistle.
    - Who (Musical group), 1982 October, 24 typed leaves
      Interview with Kenny Jones.
    - Who (Musical group), 1982 October 2, 59 typed leaves
      Interview with Pete Townshend [Two Tape Interview].
    - Who (Musical group), 1982 October 3, 27 typed leaves
      Interview with Roger Daltrey.
    - X (Musical group), 1994 January 27, 5 typed leaves
      Interview questions for Exene Cervenka and John Doe.
    - Yes (Musical group), 1984 March 30, 3 typed leaves
      Interview with Jon Anderson, summary notes.
    - Yes (Musical group), circa 1981, 5 typed leaves
      Program transcript with Trevor Rabin.
  - 2.2. Rock Chronicles Publicity Materials and Photographs, 1935-1996, bulk 1980-1996
    - .38 Special (Musical group), 1980s, 3 photographs + publicity materials (Box 47)
    - 10,000 Maniacs (Musical group), 1986-1989, 6 photographs + publicity materials
    - 13 Engines (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - 4 of Us (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - 4 Reasons Unknown (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - 54-40 (Musical group), 1986-1989, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - 9 Ways to Sunday (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - 9.9 (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - A-440 (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Aaron, Jay, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - ABBA (Musical group), 1981, publicity materials
    - ABC (Musical group), 1987, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - AC/DC (Musical group), 1980s, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Accept (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Ace of Base (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Acid Test (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ackerman, William, undated, Publicity materials
    - Acoustic Alchemy (Musical group), 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Adams, Bryan, 1984-1987, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Adams, Greg, undated, Publicity materials
    - Adrenalin (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Adventures (Musical group), 1988, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Aerosmith (Musical group), 1985-1990, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - A-ha (Musical group), 1986-1990, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Air Supply (Musical group), 1980s, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Alarm (Musical group), 1980s, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Alcatrazz (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Alexander, Gregg, 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Alice in Chains (Musical group), 1990-1993, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - All About Eve (Musical group), 1988-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Allen, Peter, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Allman Brothers Band; Allman, Gregg, 1947-, 1979-1995, 6 photographs + publicity materials
    - Almond, Marc, 1988-1993, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Alpert, Herb, 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Altered State (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Altman, Jeff, undated, Publicity materials
    - Alvin, Dave, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Amada, Maia, 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ambitious Lovers (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - America (Musical group), 1983, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - American Girls (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - American Music Club (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Amos, Tori, undated, Publicity materials
    - Ana (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Anderson, Bruford, Wakeman, Howe (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Anderson, Eric, undated, Publicity materials
    - Anderson, Laurie, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Anderson, Michael, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Angel City (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Angelis, Kim, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Animal Bag (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Animals (Musical group), 1983, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Animotion (Musical group), 1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Anka, Paul, 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Annabella, undated, Publicity materials
    - Ant, Adam, 1985-1995, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Aphex Twin, 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Apollo Smile (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Appice, Carmine, undated, Publicity materials
    - April Wine (Musical group), 1984-1985, 6 photographs + publicity materials
    - Arc Angels (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Arcade (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Arcadia (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Armageddon Dildos (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Armored Saint (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Art of Noise (Musical group); Horn, Trevor, 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Ash, Daniel, undated, Publicity materials
    - Asia (Musical group), 1982-1990, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Aslan (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ass Ponys (Musical group), 1994-1995, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Astley, Jon, 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Astley, Rick, undated, Publicity materials
    - Astley, Virginia, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Atlant's Alternative Rhythms, 1977, Publicity materials
    - Autograph (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Average White Band, circa 1981, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Aviator (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Aztec Camera (Musical group), 1987-1993, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - B.E. Taylor Group, undated, Publicity materials
    - B-52's (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Babble (Musical group), 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Baby Ford, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Babylon A.D. (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bachman Turner Overdrive, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bad Company (Musical group), 1990, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Bad English (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bad Religion (Musical group), 1995, Publicity materials
    - Baker, Ginger, 1988 December 26, Publicity materials
    - Bakers Pink (Musical group), 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Balaam & the Angel (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Balancing Act (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ball, David, 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ballard, Russ, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bambi Slam (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bananarama (Musical group), 1982-1988, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Band (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Banded Together, undated, Publicity materials
    - Bang-Bang (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Bangles (Musical group), 1984-1987, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Bardens, Pete, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Barefoot servants (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Barenaked Ladies, 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Barnes, Jimmy, 1986-1988, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Barone, Richard, 1990 April, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Barrett, Syd, 1969, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Barris, George, undated, Publicity materials
    - Barry, John, undated, Publicity materials
    - Bash & Pop (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Basia, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Baton Rouge (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Beach Boys, 1989-1990, 7 photographs + publicity materials
    - Bears (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Beat Farmers (Musical group), 1986-1987, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Beat Rodeo (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Beatles, 1967-1987, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Beats International (Musical group), 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Beautiful (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Beautiful South (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Beck, Jeff, 1976-1983, Publicity materials
    - Beck, Robin, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bee Gees, 1989-1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Been, Michael, 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Beghe, Francesca, 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bell & Shore, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Belly (Musical group), 1995, Publicity materials
    - Beloved (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Benatar, Pat, 1982-1983, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Bendik (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bennet, Pete, 1989 September 15, Publicity materials
    - Bennett, Tony, undated, Publicity materials
    - Bentyne, Cheryl, undated, Publicity materials
    - Berlin (Musical group), 1983, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Better Than Ezra (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bhatia, Amin, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Big Audio Dynamite (Musical group), 1985-1991, 3 photographs + publicity materials (Box 48)
    - Big Bam Boo (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Big Country (Musical group), 1983-1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Big Dipper (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Big Dish (Musical group), 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Big F (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Big Head Todd and the Monsters (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Big Pig (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - BiGod 20 (Musical group), 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Billy Satellite (Musical group), 1984, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Billy the Kid (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - B-Jork, undated, Publicity materials
    - Black Crowes (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Black Fish (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Black 'n Blue (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Black Sabbath (Musical group), 1982-1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Black Velvet Band, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Blackeyed Susan (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Blackfoot (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Blades, Reuben, 1985-1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Blair Quartet, undated, Publicity materials
    - Blakeley, Peter, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Blasters (Musical group), 1985-1986, Publicity materials
    - Blind Melon (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Blitzspeer (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Blondie (Musical group), 1979-1981, Publicity materials
    - Bloom, Luka, 1990-1994, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Blow Monkeys (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Blue Mercedes (Musical group), undated, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Blue Murder (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Blue Nile (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Blue Öyster Cult (Musical group), 1985-1988, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Blues Traveler (Musical group), 1994, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Blur (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - BoDeans (Musical group), 1986-1993, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Bogosian, Eric, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bolshoi (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bolton, Michael, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bon Jovi (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Bonham, Jason, 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Book of Love (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Boom Crash Opera (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Boomtown Rats (Musical group), 1985 August 29, Publicity materials